you hit the finish line in 2 hours
what do you do with the rest
so face mine
my goal is time
depending on the result
ran out of stock
I will buy again
then you go back to the supplier
buy again
go again and stay there
made 1000 tale that's it
when i learned
to optimize time and effort
using creative ways to sell
I got it there
get the salesman's neck off my forehead
make the experience work
the conversion rate increased
consequently ended better
faster my stock and leaked
so i worked 2 hours
3 hours 1:30 depends a lot and I leaked
I was rested for another day
I was in the same
vibe of the time
because if I work like a camel
today I will not be available
that i'm having here now